Up with People Archive 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series III: Scores, 1968-1994
  - Plus Haut Que Moi – Pop Medley, 1975-1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Pop Medley – Praire Rose, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Prelude – The Puzzle, 1982, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - ¿Que Te Pasa? – Medley Quebecois, 1982, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ragged Tramp’s Rhymes – Red Tide, 1981, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Reprises – Reprises for China, 1972-1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Reunion – Robbie, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Rock’ N’ Roll is Gone For Good – Rubberband Man, 1978, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Safir Ya Habibi Wir Dja – Sing For the Searchers, 1975-1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Shine on, Shine Man – Sing Out 66’, 1975-1978, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Sir Duke – Sixties Medley, 1989, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Skoczek Polka – Something in the Music, 1971, 1979, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Snowbird Canada – Space Medley Cast A, 1991, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Spain – Stand Together, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - States Medley – String around My Finger, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Sunrise – Super Bowl 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Super Bowl Run On – Swiss Medley, 1979-1982, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ta Paida Tu Pirea – Tarantella di Rossini, 1979-1988, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Te Llevare Una Rosa – Thanks to You (The United Way Jingle), 1979-1984, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - That Tumble Down Shack in Athlone – Time to Take Our Place, 1978-1991, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Together We Can Find Our Answers – Touch Somebody’s Heart, 1988-1989, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Touch Somebody’s Heart – Two Hundred Years and Just a Baby, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Umbaqanga Music – Up with People 76, 1976-1986 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Up with People! – Up with People II, 1969, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Up with People! – Up with People Overture to Act II, 1974-1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Va, Pensairo, Sull’Ali Dorate – Volare, 1977-1984, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Wabash Cannon Ball – Znad Wisty, 1970-1984, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Sheet Music, 1937-2000
  The series contains song scoressheet music used by Up with People. Sheet music contains the parts written for individual instruments within each work. The series is arranged alphabetically according to song title with several titles contained in each folder.
  - A Smile that is good for life – Another Page, 1971-1981, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Arco Jesse Owens Games – Arkansas, 1964-1997, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Barumba – Breakin’ New Ground, 1968-1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Buddies – Bye-Bye, 1970-1971, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Canada’s Heart is Out to Capture the World – Chez Loulou, 1946-1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Citizen of the year – The Crowd, 1970-1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dare! – Dreams, 1964-1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Earth 1991 – Entr’acte Encore, 1969-1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Epitaph of a Fencepost –Evviva Bari, 1966-1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Free labor will win – Festival Overture, 1983-1995, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Fifteen Minutes Intermission – Finale, 1966-1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Follow Me – The Future Starts Today, 1966-1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Gamblin Man – Going Strong, 1962-1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Golden Dream – The Golden Mandolin, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Gods Mighty Style – Great Things, 1945-1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Handle Doch Handle Gleich – Hawaii Imua, 1965-1970, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Hello Fresh Morning – Hey you, out there, 1965-1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - High School Blues – Hitch Your Wagon, 1972-1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hole in the Wall – A Hundred Years of Progress for People, 1965-1977, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Ici sur la Montagne – I’m Nobody’s doctor, 1947-1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - In Kansas – I’ll Never Fly, 1967-1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - It’s a Hershey Day – It’s your day (U.S.A.), 1969-1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Jacks –John David Sebastian Smith, 1964-1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - John Loudon – Just People, 1993-1994, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Labels – Let the Rafters Ring, 1970-1991, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Life is getting better – Lizaveta, 1966-1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Lo Spirito Fiorentino – Love can Build a Bridge, 1968-1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - My Highland Home – McCormick has the Recipe, 1946-1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - McNamara’s Band – Music to Intro. Part 2, 1964-1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Napoli, Terra Bella –Not by Wheat Alone, 1964-1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Ol’ Man Mose – Overture, 1937-2000 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Pierro’s Dance – Playing With Fire, 1968-1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Polite Melody – Present for Santa, 1971-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Progress for People – Putting the Day Together, 1972-1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Racing Song – Reprises, 1977-1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rhythm of the World – Row and Catch the Wind, 1968-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - S.A.C. – Seht Night Zurück, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Shoot for the Stars – Singout Express, 1966-1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Slogans U.S.A. – Somewhere Else, 1968-1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Special Supplement – Swing Out, 1965-1993 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - There is Something Great about a City – Terry’s Song, 1966-1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Texaco Song – Think/Respect, 1965-1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Thinking About the Days Ahead – Together We Can Find the Answers, 1969-1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Too Late to Begin – Two Islands, 1967-1989 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - U.F.O. - UWP Overture – ACT II, 1968-1999 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Up Beat & Outward – Up With People!, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Vamos a Bailar – The Volunteers of Tennessee, 1969, 1991, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Wall – Way Outside You, 1965-1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Way Outside You – We Dreamed Wild, 1969-1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - We Have Today – Wizard of Caux, 1967-1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Wonder of it All – Wyoming, 1969-1998 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - You are the Sea – You’re in Florida, 1969-1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Series V: Music Translations, 1971-1995
  The series is comprised of sheet music and scores of songs used by Up with People that have been translated into other languages. It is arranged alphabetically by language.
  - Dutch, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Dutch (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Dutch (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Dutch, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Dutch (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Dutch (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Dutch, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Dutch, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Dutch, early material to 1973 (1 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Dutch, early material to 1973 (2 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Dutch Lyrics, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Dutch Lyrics, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Dutch Lyrics, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Dutch Lyrics, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Dutch Lyrics, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Dutch Show, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - French, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - French, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - French, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - French, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - French, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - French, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - French, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - French, early material to 1974, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - French, final version (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - French, final version (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - French Lyrics, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - French Lyrics, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - French Lyrics, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - French Lyrics, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - French Lyrics, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - French Lyrics, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - French Lyrics, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - French Lyrics, World in Motion, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - French Show, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - German, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - German, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - German, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - German, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - German, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - German, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - German (1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - German (2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - German, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - German, earliest version, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - German Lyrics, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - German Lyrics, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - German Lyrics, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - German Lyrics, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - German Lyrics, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - German Lyrics, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - German Lyrics, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - German Lyrics, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - German Show, 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - German, Sing Out, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Italian, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Italian, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Italian, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Italian, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Italian, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Italian, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Italian, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Italian, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Italian, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Italian, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Italian Lyrics, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Italian Lyrics, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Italian Lyrics, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Italian Lyrics, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Italian Show, 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Italian Show, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Italian Show (1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Italian Show (2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Series VI: Symphony Arrangements, 1951-1998
  The series contains symphony arrangements produced by Up with People. Symphony arrangements are the scores for a full symphony of instruments. The series is arranged alphabetically according to symphony title.
  - Alma Llanera, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - America the Beautiful, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - American Popular Song, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Back in Style-Medley 2 (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Back in Style-Medley 2 (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Beat of the Future (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Beat of the Future (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Beat of the Future (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Breakin’ New Ground, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Can we Sing a Song of Peace, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Can we Sing a Song of Peace- Reprise, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Canadian Pacific Medley, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Canadian Railroad Trilogy, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Chante- La ta Chanson/Nova Scotia Song, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Chaser, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Chaser, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Chaser 1, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Chaser 2, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Chevaliers/Vrolijke, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Classical Medley, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Come Home, Paddy Reilly, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Coming of Age, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Country Medley, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Dajčovo Horo (1 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Dajčovo Horo (2 of 2), undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Earth Ship, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Entracte, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Entr’acte Act 2, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Eres Tu, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Everday Heros, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Festa Humana, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Fjäriln Vingad Syns På Haga, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Fifty’s Prom (1), undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Fifty’s Prom (2), undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Final Chaser, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Galway Shawl, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Give the Children back their Childhood, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Go for it all, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Good Guys, Bad Guys, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Gopak, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Gopak, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Grandad’s Wooden Chain, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - If There is Love, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - It Takes a Whole Village, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - International Medley, 1978-1982 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - I’s the B’y, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - El Jarabe Tapatio, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - John David Sebastian Smith, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Jota de Alegría, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Just People, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - La Bamba, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - La Bikina, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - La Costilla, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - La Negra, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - La Petite Gayole/Vrolijke Vrienden, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - La Song Part 1 and 2, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Lanigan’s Ball, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Let the River Flow (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Let the River Flow (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Let there be Peace on Earth, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Look for the People, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Mi Ciudad, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Moldavian Dance, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Mon Pays/Nova Scotia Song, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Moon Rider, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Mule Skinner Blues, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Oak Tree, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Oberek Opoczynski, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - One-shot Deal, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Our Friendship Deep and Long, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Overture- Act II, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Overture for the Eighties (1 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Overture for the Eighties (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Overture (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Overture (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Overture, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Overture (1 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Overture (2 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Overture (3 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Overture (4 of 4), undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Pays de Coeur-Hartelijk Land, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Play-off #1, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Play-off #1-2, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Play-off #2, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Pop Medley 20s, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Pop Medley 30s, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Pop Medley 40s, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Prelude, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - El Puente, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - El Puente- Reprise, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Push on Through (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Push on Through (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Push on Through (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Raise a Ruckus Tonight, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - El Rasca Petate, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Ready or Not, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Ready or Not/Energy, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Reprises, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Reprises, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Reprises, 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Reprises (1 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Reprises (2 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Reunion (1 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Reunion (2 of 2), undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Roads ’98, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Rock ‘n’ Roll is Gone for Good, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Room for Everyone, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Shule Aroon, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Sixties Medley, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Sixties Medley, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Someday’s Child, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Skoczek Polka, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Stand Together (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Stand Together (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Strings on Fire!, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Take the Cake (1 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Take the Cake (2 of 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Thank You, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - There’s Gonna be Another Day, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - A Thousand Suns, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Throw me the Ball, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Till Everyone is Home, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Time to take our Place, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Together we can find the Answers, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Tomorrow’s a Picture, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Uncle Victor and Auntie Ola, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Up with People!, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Up with People!, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Up with People!, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Up with People!, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Up with People!- Opening, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Up with People!/Reprises (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Up with People!/Reprises (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Walk Lightly (1 of 2), undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Walk Lightly, undated (Box 29, Folder 13 (2 of 2))
  - The Walk of Ed White, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Walk on Through (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Walk on Through (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Wayfarer, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - The Way I feel, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Way Outside You, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - We are Many, We are One (1 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - We are Many, We are One (2 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - We are Many- Reprise, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - We Believe in the Tennessee Valley, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Wel Anne-Marieken, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - We’ll be There, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - We Shall Over Come, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - We Wish you Happiness, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - What Color is God’s Skin?, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - What Color is God’s Skin?, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Whatcha Gonna Do?, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - When We Shine, They Shine, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Where the Roads Come Together, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Whole Other Thing, 1973-1977 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Winners and Losers, undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - A Winter Festival, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Winter Games, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - With Everything Changing, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Wó Men de Yǒu Yí Shēn Yóu Cháng, undated (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - World in Motion, undated (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - The Wonder of it all, undated (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Ya se Van Les Pastores, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - You and Me, undated (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - You’re in Florida, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - You are the Sea, undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - You’re the Voice, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - You are what you do, undated (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Yugoslavia Folk Dance, undated (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Yellow Rose of Texas, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Y Viva España, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Znad Wisely (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Znad Wisely (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Zorba, undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Series VII: Photographic material, 1960-2010
  This series is composed of photographs, negatives, and slides and photographic albums documenting various events, performances, and notable figures involved with Up with People. The series is divided into five subseries.
  - Subseries 1: 35mm negatives, undated
    The 35mm negatives in this subseries have no title or date affixed to the negative envelope. The envelopes are numbered and are arranged alphabetically and by original numerical order.
    - Pace Japan, Asia, Korea, Africa (1 of 2), undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Pace Japan, Asia, Korea, Africa (2 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Pace Mexico, Europe (1 of 2), undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Pace Mexico, Europe (2 of 2), undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - US 1289 to 1411 (1 of 2), undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - US 1289 to 1411 (2 of 2), undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - US 1437 to 1789 (1 of 2), undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - US 1437 to 1789 (2 of 2), undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - US 1790 to 2150 (1 of 2), undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - US 1790 to 2150 (2 of 2), undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - US 2151 to 2339, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - US 2340 to 2499, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - US 2500 to 2824 (1 of 2), undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - US 2500 to 2824 (2 of 2), undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - US 2825 to 3784 (1 of 2), undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - US 2825 to 3784 (2 of 2), undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 2: Marketing, 1965-2010
    This series contains photographs, negatives and slides that pertain to publicity and the promotion of Up with People. It is arranged alphabetically.
    - Admissions, miscellaneous, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Billboards, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Business, Management, Leadership skills, 1992, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Color Gels, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Commercials, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Commercials, Recordings, Mexico TV, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Display photos, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Displays, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Fifteen year Review, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Gallery photo selection, 1965-1999 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Glossies, Ken Ashby, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Glossies, Associated Press Luncheon, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Glossies, Beat of the Future, undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Glossies, Belgium, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Glossies, Cast A, 1969-2001 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Glossies, Cast A, B, C, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Glossies, Cast B, 1970-1994 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Glossies, Cast C, 1970-2001 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Glossies, Cast D, 1983-2000 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Glossies, Cast E, 1981-2000 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Glossies, China, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Glossies, Charles Conrad, astronaut, undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Glossies, Drafts and captions, undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Glossies, Expo, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Glossies, Face to Face, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Glossies, The Festival, undated (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Glossies, Frank Fields, undated (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Glossies, French Language, undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Glossies, Germany, Munich Olympics, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Glossies, Graphics, undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Glossies, Hawaii, Cast C, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Glossies, Host Families, undated (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Glossies, Japan, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Glossies, London Bridge, Group Hill and Stairs, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Glossies, London Bridge, under bridge, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Glossies, London Bridge, Waterboats, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Glossies, Merchandise, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Glossies, Merchandise, undated (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - Glossies, Merchandise UWP shop, Beat of the Future, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - Glossies, Mexico, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Glossies, Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Glossies, NASA, undated (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Glossies, John Ostlund, undated (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - Glossies, John Paul II, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - Glossies, Promotional Material, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    - Glossies, Promotional Material, 1983-1985 (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - Glossies, Promotional Material, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 47)
    - Glossies, Promotional Material, undated (Box 47, Folder 48)
    - Glossies, Promotional Photo Album, 1970-1979 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Glossies, Puerto Rico, 1974-1976 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Glossies, ROTW, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Glossies, Smithfields, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Glossies, Spain, 1969-1981 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Glossies, Spanish Language, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Glossies, Super Bowl X, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Glossies, Super Bowl XIV, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Glossies, Super Bowl XVI, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 9)